

PROFILE

22-year-old Multimedia graduate, currently completing BIS Multimedia Honours at the University of Pretoria.

Confident Multimedia Designer with an eye for engaging, interactive experiences. Deadline-oriented with a background in managing designs from concept to implementation. Organized and dependable individual successful at managing multiple

Enthusiastic team player ready to contribute to company success

© CONTACT ME



+27 71 605 3079



stopie414@gmail.com



116 Kronkel Ave, Pretoria



in) <u>Reinhard Stoop</u>

SKILLS

DIGITAL MEDIA DESIGN

•••••

JAVASCRIPT, HTML, CSS

•••••

C#, C++, JAVA, PHP, XML

•••••

REACT, NODE

•••••

ADOBE SUITE

•••••

MICROSOFT SUITE

•••••

(ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- Runner up best third year
- Best final year project

REINHARD **STOOP**

BIS Multimedia Graduate



EDUCATION

HOËRSKOOL OVERKRUIN

NSC Matric (2014-2018) Bachelors pass

UNIVERSITY OF PRETORIA

BIS Multimedia Cum Laude (2019 - 2021) BIS (HONS) Multimedia (Jan 2022 - present)



WORK EXPERIENCE

Assistant Lecturer

UNIVERSITY OF PRETORIA (APR 2022 - PRESENT)

- Prepared and organized different teaching aids for use in the classroom.
- Initiated and facilitated classroom discussions.
- Selected and designed lesson plans and curriculum to meet academic objectives.
- Utilized distance learning technology to instruct students remotely.
- Handled an HCI module and managed the UI/UX projects.

Tutor

UNIVERSITY OF PRETORIA (FEB 2021 - JUL 2021)

- Tutor for course code IMY210
- Provided appropriate learning materials for students.
- Tutored diverse groups of students to strengthen subject comprehension, boost confidence and build important learning skills.

Brand Designer

SMARTEN (APR 2020 - SEPT 2020)

- Conceptualized brand identity and developed unique accompanying graphic style and tone for use in communications.
- · Monitored online advertising and social media campaigns to assess success of different strategies.

LANGUAGE

- Native Afrikaans
- English